myglassart.org 2011-05-25

# Privacy Policy | myglassart

### Effective June 1, 2008 

Frabel Art Foundation, Inc. (“Frabel” or “we”) operates MyGlassArt.org. This Privacy Policy describes Frabel’s use and sharing of personally information (“PI”-- your full name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, or credit card number) that Members voluntarily provide to Frabel when they register (also known as “Registration PI”). The Term “User” refers to a any Visitor or Member. This Privacy Policy applies to the services offered by Frabel, including any Frabel-branded URL (the “Frabel Website”), the Frabel messaging services, and any other features, content, or applications offered from time to time by Frabel in connection with the Frabel Website (collectively, the “Frabel Services”). The Frabel Services are hosted in the United States.

The Frabel Website is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect PI from children under 13 years of age. 

From time to time Frabel may modify this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, our PI collection and use practices, the features of the Frabel Services, or technology, and such modifications shall be effective upon posting by Frabel on the Frabel Website. Your continued use of the Frabel Services after Frabel posts a revised Privacy Policy signifies your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. It is therefore important that you review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are updated as to any changes. If Frabel materially changes its practices regarding collection or use of your PI, your PI will continue to be governed by the Policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of, and have not objected to, the change. 

### Collection and Submission of PI and Non-PI on MyGlassArt.org

When Frabel collects PI from you it is because you are voluntarily submitting Registration PI to us in order to register as a Member of Frabel. Frabel may also collect PI from you if you choose to participate in Frabel Services activities like sweepstakes, contests, and surveys, because you want us to furnish you with products, services, newsletters, or information, or in connection with content or suggestions you submit to Frabel for review. 

In addition, Frabel collects other non-PI including IP address, aggregate user data, and browser type. This data is used to manage and improve the Frabel Services, track usage, and for security purposes.  
MyGlassArt.org Members may also choose to provide or store non-PI information in their profiles, including but not limited to date of birth, interests, hobbies, lifestyle choices, groups with whom they are affiliated (schools, companies), videos and/or pictures, private messages, bulletins or personal statements (collectively “Profile Information”). The Profile Information in a Member’s profile is provided at his or her sole discretion.

Frabel Members can change their Registration PI and Profile Information at any time and can control how Visitors, other Members and Frabel communicate with them by controlling their account settings, available within the “Edit Profile” portion of their Frabel profile. Link to Privacy Settings.  
Cookies: MyGlassArt.org may use cookes to identify your Internet browser, store Users’ preferences, and determine whether you have installed the enabling software needed to access certain material on the Frabel Services. Data in cookies may be read to authenticate user sessions or provide services.  
Third party advertisements displayed on Frabel Services may also contain cookies set by Internet advertising companies or advertisers (known as “third party cookies”). Frabel does not control these third party cookies and Users of the Frabel Services should check the privacy policy of the Internet advertising company or advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies. See the “Notice” section below for more information on customized advertising on Frabel. A pixel tag is a tiny image inserted in a webpage and used to record the number and types of views for that page. Frabel may allow third party pixel tags to be present on Frabel Services for purposes of advertising, providing services or data and statistics collection.  
You can program your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent and block third party cookies or block all cookies. However, by blocking all cookies you may not have access to certain features on the Frabel Services.

### NOTICE: Frabel Will Provide You with Notice about its PI Collection Practices

When you voluntarily provide PI to Frabel, we will make sure you are informed about who is collecting the information, how and why the information is being collected and the types of uses Frabel will make of the information to the extent it is being used in a manner that differs from what is allowed pursuant to this Privacy Policy.

At the time you provide your PI, Frabel will notify you of your options regarding our use of your PI (See “Choice” below). Except as described in this Privacy Policy, Frabel will not share your PI with third parties unless you have given Frabel permission to do so (See “Use” below).

Frabel Services may be linked to Internet sites operated by other companies. Frabel Services may also carry advertisements from other companies. Frabel is not responsible for the privacy practices of websites or other services operated by third parties that are linked to or integrated with the Frabel Services or for the privacy practices of third party Internet advertising companies. Once you leave Frabel Services via such a link, access a third party application (such as widgets) or click on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine, among other things, how they will handle any PI they collect from you.  
Frabel Services may also be linked to sites operated by companies affiliated with Frabel. Users who visit those Affiliated Company sites should still refer to their separate privacy policies and practices, which may differ from this Privacy Policy.

Frabel may use cookies and similar tools to customize the content and advertising you receive based on the Profile Information you have provided. Profile Information you provide in structured profile fields or questions (“Structured Profile Information”), information you add to open-ended profile fields and questions (“Non-Structured Profile Information”) and other non-PI about you may also be used to customize the online ads you encounter to those we believe are aligned with your interests. The information used for this feature does not provide your PI or identify you as an individual to third parties. If you would like to disable advertising customization for Non-Structured Profile Information, please log in and change your personal settings. 

Some of the advertisements that appear on Frabel Services may also be delivered to you by third party Internet advertising companies. These companies utilize certain technologies to deliver advertisements and marketing messages and to collect non-PI about your visit to or use of Frabel Services, including information about the ads they display, via a cookie placed on your computer that reads your IP address. To opt out of information collection by these companies, please go to your personal settings.

Third party applications (such as widgets) created by third party developers may also be available on the Frabel Services. Third party applications are small bits of software, often with interactivity, that can be installed into Members’ profiles or shared with other Users. However, Frabel does not control the third party developers, and cannot dictate their actions. When a Member engages with a third party application, that Member is interacting with the third party developer, not with Frabel. Frabel encourages Members not to provide PI to the third party’s application unless the Member knows the party with whom it is interacting. 

### CHOICE: Frabel Will Provide You with Choices about the Use of Your PI

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, Frabel will get your permission before we use the PI you provide to us in a way that is inconsistent with the purpose for which it was submitted or share your PI with third parties that are not affiliated with Frabel.

### USE: Frabel’s Use of PI

Frabel will only use the PI you provide under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If Frabel obtains PI from a third party, such as a business partner, our use of that information is also governed by this Privacy Policy. 

In order to locate other Frabel Members that you may already know in the physical world, Frabel allows Users to search for Members using Registration PI (i.e., full name or email address). Frabel also allows Users to browse for certain Profile Information in order to help connect with Members (i.e., schools and/or companies where Users may have attended or worked). Frabel may also enable Members to publicly display some Registration PI as an element of their Profile Information if they choose to do so via a profile setting under “Edit Profile.” Search engines may index the portion of a Member’s profile (including the Profile Information it contains) that is publicly displayed. 

If you have consented to receive promotional materials (e.g., newsletters) or notifications from Frabel, Frabel may periodically use your email address to send you such materials related to the Frabel Services, as applicable. If you want to stop receiving such materials from Frabel, you can change your profile settings under “Account Settings,” or follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.  
Frabel employees, agents and contractors must have a business reason to obtain access to your PI. Frabel may share your PI with those who help us manage or provide Frabel Services’ information activities, or with outside contractors, agents or sponsors who help us with the administration, judging and prize fulfillment aspects of contests, promotions and sweepstakes. 

These outside contractors, agents or sponsors may temporarily store some information on their servers, but they may only use your PI to provide Frabel with a specific service and not for any other purpose. Frabel may also provide your PI to a third party in those instances where you have chosen to receive certain information and have been notified that the fulfillment of such a request requires the sharing of your PI. Frabel also may share your PI with Affiliated Companies if it has a business reason to do so.

As described in “Notice” above, Frabel may customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive on the MyGlassArt.org website, or may work with outside companies to do so. Your non-PI and/or Profile Information may be shared with these companies so this customization can be accomplished. Frabel prohibits these companies from sharing your non-PI and/or Profile Information with any third party or from using it for any other purpose. Anonymous click stream, number of page views calculated by pixel tags, and aggregated demographic information may also be shared with Frabel’s advertisers and business partners.

There may be instances when Frabel may access or disclose PI, Profile Information or non-PI without providing you a choice in order to: (i) protect or defend the legal rights or property of Frabel, our Affiliated Companies or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (ii) protect the safety and security of Users of the Frabel Services or members of the public including acting in urgent circumstances; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or (iv) comply with the law or legal process. In addition, if Frabel sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of all or a material part of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, Frabel may transfer your PI to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

When a Member who is located in the European Union chooses to post Profile Information that will be publicly disclosed, that Member is responsible for ensuring that such information conforms to all local data protection laws. Frabel is not responsible under the EU local data protection laws for Member-posted information. 

### SECURITY: Frabel Protects the Security of PI

Frabel uses commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard PI and credit card information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. In addition, Frabel uses reasonable methods to make sure that PI is accurate, up-to-date and appropriately complete. 

### ACCESS, REMEDIES AND COMPLIANCE: How to Access, Correct or Change Your Preferences regarding PI and How to Contact Frabel About Privacy Concerns

Whenever possible, Frabel Members may review the Registration PI we maintain about them in our records. We will take reasonable steps to correct any PI a Member informs us is incorrect. If you are a Member, you can view and change your Registration PI, Member preferences and Profile Information by logging into your account and accessing features such as “Edit Profile” and “Account Settings.” 

If you ask Frabel to stop using your PI, Frabel will honor that request while retaining any record of your PI that is necessary to comply with applicable federal, state or local law.

If you would like to communicate with us about this Privacy Policy or Frabel’s collection and use of your PI please contact Frabel at:privacy@myglassart.org

Mail: 689 Antone St NW. Atlanta, GA 30318
